# **Ayush Kumar Singh**

# **UX/Frontend Engineer**

ayush.singh.xda@gmail.com • +91 7011 439 788 • Noida, India • www.ayushsingh.net

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a professional UI/UX Designer and Front end developer. I like to take responsibility for crafting end to end User Experience from prototyping to develop the actual product. I help to craft memorable user experiences using modern frontend architecture.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



**DLT** UI/UX DESIGNER

DLT Labs Private Limited, Noida

December 2019 - PRESENT



**UX ENGINEER** 

SOE Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Noida

July 2019 - November 2019



**G** UX ENGINEER

Software Incubator, AKGEC

September 2016 - May 2019

### **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Angular
- HTML/CSS
- Git
- SVG Animation
- User Interface Design
- UX Design
- Responsive Web Design

### **TOOLS**

- Figma, Sketch, Invision
- Adobe Creative Suite

# **PROJECTS**

10+ personal / professional projects viewable at portfolio: www.ayushsingh.net

#### **EDUCATION**



B.Tech - Information Technology

AJAY KUMAR GARG ENGINEERING COLLEGE, (AKTU)

2015-2019

# 🔛 Elementary Education DMA, Meerut (CBSE) 2004-2014

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- HTML / CSS Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2018
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2017
- SVG Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2017
- 1st position in Web and Graphic Design hackathon, ABES ACM 2017
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2016
- Lead Designer at AKGEC College Fest, 2016
- Recognized Themer at xda-developers.com, 2014

## EXTRAS

Competitive Powerlifting

- 1st position, AKGEC, 2018
- 2nd position, AKGEC 2017
- 2nd position, COT GBPU, 2017
- 2nd position, AKGEC 2016